Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part I WAG.025.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Foreign Countries (arranged alphabetically by country)
  - Japan, Jun 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Latvia, 1940-1946 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Lithuania, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Lithuania, Jan 1940-Jul 1940 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Lithuania, Aug 1940-Dec 1940 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    Reel#: 93
  - Lithuania, Jan 1941-May 1941 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lithuania, 1943-1947 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Luxembourg, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Mexico, 1937-1940 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Mexico, Jan 1941-Jun 1941 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Mexico, Jul 1941-Oct 1941 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Mexico, Nov 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Mexico, 1942, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Mexico, Jan 1942-Feb 1942 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Reel#: 94
  - Mexico, Mar 1942-Apr 1942 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Mexico, May 1942-Jun 1942 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Mexico, Jul 1942-Aug 1942 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Mexico, Sep 1942-Oct 1942 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Mexico, Nov 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Mexico, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Mexico, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Reel#: 95
  - Mexico, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Mexico, Jan 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Mexico, Jul 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Mexico, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Mexico, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Netherlands, 1942-1944 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Netherlands, 1946-1947 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Norway, 1943-1947 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Palestine, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Palestine, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    Reel#: 96
  - Palestine, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Palestine, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Palestine, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Palestine, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Poland, 1939-1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 97
  - Poland, 1943 (undated) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Poland, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Poland, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Poland, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Poland, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Poland, Jan 1946 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Reel#: 98
  - Poland, Feb 1946 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Poland, Mar 1946 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Poland, Apr 1946 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Poland, May 1946 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Poland, Jun 1946 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Poland, Jul 1946 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Poland, Aug 1946 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Poland, Sep 1946 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Poland, Oct 1946 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Reel#: 99
  - Poland, Nov 1946 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Poland, Dec 1946 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Poland, Jan 1947 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Poland, Feb 1947 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Poland, Mar 1947 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Poland, Apr 1947 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Poland, May 1947 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Poland, Jun 1947 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    Reel#: 100
  - Poland, Jul 1947 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Poland, Aug 1947 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Poland, Sep 1947 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Reel#: 101
  - Poland, Oct 1947 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Poland, Nov 1947 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Poland, Dec 1947 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Portugal, 1940-1942 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Roumania, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Roumania, 1941-1943 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Roumania, 1944-1946 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Roumania, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - South Africa, 1941-1947 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Spain, 1942-1947 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Reel#: 102
  - Sweden, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, 1939-1942 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, Jan 1945-Aug 1945 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, Sep 1945 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, Oct 1945 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, Nov 1945 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, Dec 1945 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    Reel#: 103
  - Sweden, 1946, undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
    Reel#: 104
  - Sweden, Jan 1946 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, Feb 1946 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Sweden, Mar 1946 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    Reel#: 105
  - Sweden, Apr 1946 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Sweden, May 1946 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Sweden, Jun 1946 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Reel#: 106
  - Sweden, Jul 1946 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, Aug 1946 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, Sep 1946 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Reel#: 107
  - Sweden, Oct 1946 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, Nov 1946 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, Dec 1946 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Reel#: 108
  - Sweden, 1947, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, Jan 1947 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Sweden, Feb 1947 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, Mar 1947 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Reel#: 109
  - Sweden, Apr 1947 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, May 1947 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, Jun 1947 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, Jul 1947 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Reel#: 110
  - Sweden, Aug 1947 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, Sep 1947 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, Oct 1947 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Reel#: 111
  - Sweden, Nov 1947 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, Dec 1947 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Switzerland, 1940-1943 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Switzerland, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Reel#: 112
  - Switzerland, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Switzerland, 1946 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Switzerland, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Turkey, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Uruguay, 1945-1947 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Venezuela, 1941-1945 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Yugoslavia, 1941-1944, 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Rescue and Relief
  - Subseries IV:A: Rescue
    - Sub Subseries IV:A:1: General
      - Rescue, 1934-1936 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Rescue, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Rescue, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Rescue: Lists of Names: Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Rescue, 1940, undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Rescue: Biographies (Individual), 1940-1942 (Box 38, Folder 21)
        Reel#: 113
      - Rescue, Jan 1940-Jun-40 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Rescue: Lists of Refugees in France and Lithuania, Summer 1940 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Rescue: Lists Presented to AFL (I, II, and III), Jul 1940-Aug 1940 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Rescue: Lists, with Biographical Information, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Rescue, Jul 1940 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Rescue, Aug 1940 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Rescue, Sep 1, 1940-Sep 15, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Rescue, Sep 16, 1940-Sep 30, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Rescue, Oct 1, 1940-Oct 15, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        Reel#: 114
      - Rescue, Oct 16, 1940-Oct 31, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Rescue, Nov 1, 1940-Nov 15, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Rescue, Nov 16, 1940-Nov 30, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Rescue, Dec 1, 1940-Dec 15, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Rescue, Dec 16, 1940-Dec 31, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Sub Subseries IV:A:2: D.P. Case Files: Europe, 1940-1941
      - Abendsztern, Hersz Lajb and wife, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 11)
        Reel#: 115
      - Aronson, Chil, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Avraschoff, Gregor, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Banchewsky, Abram, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Banewur, Eva, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Bienstock, Serge and Eva, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - Blanc, Juliette Francoise, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - Blum, Joseph and Henriette, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - Blumel, Andre, Jean and Sara, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - Braun, Stanislaw and Sonia, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - Bursztejn, Joseph, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - Caballero, Largo and Rodolfo Llopis, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - Fenster, Herman and family, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - Frejlich, Jozef and Dora, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - Frenkel, Nussen and Chana, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - Gerb, Louis, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - Giacometti, Guido, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - Golkbergas, Semion and parents, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - Goldstein, Anatole and family, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - Graubert-Grubert, Paul Pinkus, Florentine and Hanna, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - Gurfinkel, David and family, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - Guzowsky, Borach and family, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - Januskis, Jan and Vera, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - Karafiol, Pinchas, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - Kautsky, Benedikt, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 35)
      - Kautsky, Luise, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 36)
      - Kiviliovitch, Moisei and family, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 37)
      - Knopf, Lajb and Yenty, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - Levinson, Paul, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - Lissim, Simon and Irene, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - Mandelman, Peretz, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - Mandelstamm, Maxime and Helene, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - Marszak, Jsrael-Oszer, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - Minc, Alexander and Raszel, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - Najman, Chiel and family, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - Olberg, Paul and Frieda, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 46)
      - Polak, Berta and Jean-Claude, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - Rapoport, Selman and Ides, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - Rosenthal, Leo, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 49)
      - Sapir, Alexander and family, 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 50)
      - Scheiner, David, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 51)
      - Scheiner, Joseph and family, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 52)
      - Schwartz, Simcha, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 53)
      - Stencel, Zygmunt, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 54)
      - Stenders, Ilja, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 55)
      - Steren, Esther, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Stiassny, Else and Michael, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Tresso, Pietro and Barbara Debora Seidenfeld, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Wachtel, Israel, 1941-1945 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Weiler, Ritta and Robert, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Weinberg, Elias and Elise, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Zborovsky, Galina, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Zyskand, Chaim, Ethel, Judith, Leon and Wolf, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Zysman, Abram and family, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Sub Subseries IV:A:3: D.P. Case Files: Japan, 1941
      - Bekerkunc, Herschel, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Broder, Tobka, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 11)
        Reel#: 116
      - Engelsberg, Abram, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Finkelstein, Izaak, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Fiszman, Yankiel Hersz, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Fuks, Maria, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Gabai, Sora, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Ginsburg, Kalmen, Debra and Betty, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Goldgamer, Efroim, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - Golomb, Stefan and Freda, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      - Gryfenberg, Jakub, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Hershenhorn, J., 1941 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Kassel, Felicia and Syzmon, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Katulanski, Baruch, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Miller, Icchok, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Panski, Waclaw, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Perkal, Szlama-Fajwel, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Pizitz, Mendel, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Rajzman, Wiktor, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 28)
      - Rozen, Bella and Ber, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Rubinstein, Jonas and Sami, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Shymkin, Joseph, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Spira, Majer Isaak, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Szemen, Chana, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - Winograd, Israel, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - Rescue: France Speaks, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Rescue, Jan 1, 1941-Jan 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - Rescue, Jan 16, 1941-Jan 31, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - Rescue, Feb 1, 1941-Feb 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 38)
        Reel#: 117
      - Rescue, Feb 16, 1941-Feb 28, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - Rescue, Mar 1, 1941-Mar 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Rescue, Mar 16, 1941-Mar 31, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - Rescue, Apr 1, 1941-Apr 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 42)
      - Rescue, Apr 16, 1941-Apr 30, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - Rescue, May 1, 1941-May 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Rescue, May 16, 1941-May 31, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 45)
        Reel#: 118
      - Rescue, Jun 1, 1941-Jun 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 46)
      - Rescue, Jun 16, 1941-Jun 30, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 47)
      - Rescue, Jul 1, 1941-Jul 15, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 48)
      - Rescue, Jul 16, 1941-Jul 31, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Rescue, Aug 1941 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Rescue, Sep 1941 (Box 41, Folder 3)
        Reel#: 119
      - Rescue, Oct 1941 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Rescue, Nov 1941 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Rescue, Dec 1941 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Rescue: German and Austrian Socialists and Labor Activists, 1941-1942 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        Reel#: 120
      - Rescue: Card File: Biographies of People Rescued by JLC, 1940-1942 (Box 41, Folder 7A)
      - Rescue: France Speaks, 1942 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Rescue, Jan 1942 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Rescue, Feb 1942 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Rescue, Mar 1942 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Rescue, Apr 1942 (Box 41, Folder 12)
        Reel#: 121
      - Rescue, May 1942 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Rescue, Jun 1942 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Rescue, Jul 1942 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Rescue, Aug 1942 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Rescue, Sep 1942 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Rescue, Oct 1942 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Rescue, Nov 1942 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Rescue, Dec 1942 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Rescue: France Speaks, 1943 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Rescue, 1943 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Rescue, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Rescue, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 24)
        Reel#: 122
      - Rescue, Jan 1945-Jun 1945 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Rescue, Jul 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Rescue, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Rescue, Jan 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Rescue, Oct 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Rescue: Quoddy Project, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Rescue: Relative Search, [1947?] (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Rescue, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 8)
        Reel#: 123
      - Rescue, Jan 1947-Mar 1947 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Rescue, Apr 1947-May 1947 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Rescue, Jun 1947 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Rescue, Jul 1947-Aug 1947 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Rescue, Sep 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Rescue: Nathan (Nahum) Gierowitz: Germany, Jun 1946-May 1947 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Rescue: Nathan (Nahum) Gierowitz: Germany, Jun 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 42, Folder 15)
        Reel#: 124
      - Rescue: Bella Meiksin: Germany, Jan 1947-Sep 1947 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Rescue: Bella Meiksin: Germany, Oct 1947 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Rescue: Bella Meiksin: Germany, Nov 1947 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Rescue: Bella Meiksin: Germany, Dec 1947 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Rescue: United Nations, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Rescue: United Nations, Jan 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 42, Folder 21)
        Reel#: 125
      - Rescue: United Nations, Apr 1946-Jul 1946 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Rescue: United Nations, Aug 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Rescue: United Nations, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Rescue: United Nations, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Concentration Camps: Auschwitz (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Concentration Camps: Bergen-Belsen (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Concentration Camps: Buchenwald (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Concentration Camps: Dachau (Box 43, Folder 4)
        Reel#: 126
      - Concentration Camps: Joel Zak et al., "Martyred Jews of Dachau" (typescript) A-G (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Concentration Camps: J. Zak, et al., "Martyred Jews of Dachau" (typescript) H-M (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Concentration Camps: J. Zak, et al., "Martyred Jews of Dachau" (typescript) N-Z (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Concentration Camps: Lists of Jews Transferred from Dachau (typescript) A-G (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Concentration Camps: Lists of Jews Transferred from Dachau (typescript) H-M (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Concentration Camps: Lists of Jews Transferred from Dachau (typescript) N-Z (Box 43, Folder 10)
        Reel#: 127
  - Subseries IV:B: Relief
    - Sub Subseries IV:B:1: General
      - Relief: General, 1934-1937 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Relief: General, 1939-1939 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Relief: General, Jan 1940-Feb 1940 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Relief: General, Mar 1940 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Relief: General, Apr 1940 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        Reel#: 128
      - Relief: General, May 1940 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Relief: General, Jun 1940-Jul 1940 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Relief: General, Aug 1940-Sep 1940 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Relief: General, Oct 1940-Dec 1940 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Relief: General, Jan 1941-Jun 1941 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Relief: General, Jul 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Relief: General, 1942, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 129
      - Relief: General, Jan 1942-Feb 1942 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Relief: General, Mar 1942-Apr 1942 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Relief: General, May 1942-Jun 1942 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Relief: General, Jul 1942-Aug 1942 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Relief: General, Sep 1942-Oct 1942 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Relief: General, Nov 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        Reel#: 130
      - Relief: General, Jan 1943-Feb 1943 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Relief: General, Mar 1943-Apr 1943 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Relief: General, May 1943-Sep 1943 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Relief: General, Oct 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Relief: General, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Relief: General, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        Reel#: 131
      - Relief: General, Jan 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Relief: General, Jul 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Relief: General, Jan 1947-Jun 1947 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Relief: General, Jul 1947-Dec 1947 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Relief: Books, Jun 1946, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 18)
        Reel#: 132
      - Relief: Clothing, Jan 1941-Nov 1941 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Relief: Clothing, Dec 1941 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Relief: Clothing, Jan 1942-Apr 1942 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Relief: Clothing, May 1942-Sep 1942 (Box 44, Folder 22)
        Reel#: 133
      - Relief: Clothing, Oct 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Relief: Clothing, Jan 1943-Feb 1943 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Relief: Clothing, Mar 1943-May 1943 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Relief: Clothing, Jun 1943-Oct 1943 (Box 45, Folder 1A)
      - Relief: Clothing, Nov 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Relief: Clothing, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 3)
        Reel#: 134
      - Relief: Clothing, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Relief: Clothing, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Relief: France, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Relief: Poland, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Relief: Poland, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Relief: Poland, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Relief: Poland, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Relief: Poland, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Relief: Poland, Jan 1946-Mar 1946 (Box 45, Folder 12)
        Reel#: 135
      - Relief: Poland, Apr 1946-Jun 1946 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Relief: Poland, Jul 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Relief: Poland, Oct 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Relief: Poland, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jan 1941-Jul 1941 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Aug 1941 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Sep 1941-Dec 1941 (Box 45, Folder 20)
        Reel#: 136
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jan 1942 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Feb 1942 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Mar 1942 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Apr 1942 (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, May 1942 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 137
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jun 1942 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jul 1942-Aug 1942 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Sep 1942-Dec 1942 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jan 1943-Mar 1943 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Apr 1943-Jun 1943 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jul 1943-Sep 1943 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Oct 1943-Dec 1943 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jan 1944-Jun 1944 (Box 46, Folder 9)
        Reel#: 138
      - Relief: Soviet Union, Jul 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Relief: Log of Letters from the Soviet Union (in Polish, Russian, and German), 1944-1945 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Relief: Log of Letters from the Soviet Union (in Yiddish), 1944-1946 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Relief: Log of Telegrams to and from the Soviet Union, 1945-1946 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Relief: Soviet Union, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Relief: Soviet Union Series IV:C Immigration/Aid, 1946-1947 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Affidavits, 1941-1942 (Box 47, Folder 1)
        Reel#: 139
      - Aid: Clothing, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Aid: Clothing, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Aid: Food, 1945-1947 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Aid: General, 1937, 1945-1947 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Aid: Individuals, 1942-1944 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Aid: Individuals, 1945-1947 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Aid: Soviet Union, 1943-1947 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Aid: Transportation, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Aid: United National Clothing Collection, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        Reel#: 140
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Jan 1944-May 1944 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Jun 1944-Oct 1944 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Nov 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Jan 1945-Jun 1945 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Jul 1945-Sep 1945 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Oct 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Jan 1946-May 1946 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Jun 1946-Dec 1946 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - American Red Cross, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Anti-Semitism, 1940-1944 (Box 47, Folder 22A)
      - Anti-Semitism in Germany, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 23)
        Reel#: 141
      - Aufbau, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 23A)
      - Australia, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Austria, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Austria, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Austrian Refugees, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Bessarabian Federation of American Jews, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - Book Fund, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Book Fund, 1946-1947 (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - Budgets, 1941-1943 (Box 47, Folder 31)
      - Canada, 1940-1947 (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - CARE, 1945-1947 (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - Central Committee of Liberated Jews: Germany, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - Central Location Index, ca.1945 (Box 47, Folder 35)
      - Chaplains, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - Chest for the Liberation of Workers in Europe, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 36A)
      - Children, 1939-1947 (Box 47, Folder 37)
      - China, 1944-1947 (Box 47, Folder 38)
      - Clippings, Jul 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 47, Folder 39)
        Reel#: 142
      - Clippings, Jan 1947-Sep 1947 (Box 47, Folder 40)
      - Committee for the Study of Recent Immigration from Europe, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: General, 1938, 1942-1945 (Box 48, Folder 2)